<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Vault of the incarnates</title><link>https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Vault of the incarnates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:18:43 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terros</title><link>https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/terros/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:18:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/terros/</guid><description>Terros is the second boss we will be killing. Terros is a stationary boss in the center of the room, the room gets smaller as we play every 90 seconds the boss will cast Resonating Anniliation which will remove 1/4th of the room after 4 cast we wipe. Rockblast The second mechanic we have to deal with is Rockblast and Awakened Earth. Rockblast is a simple soak. after the ability has been soaked a few marked players will get the Awakened Earth which will create a stone pillar that needs to be destroyed.</description></item><item><title>Primal Counsil</title><link>https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/primal-counsil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:17:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/primal-counsil/</guid><description>This boss is the third boss we will take on. The primal council is not super complex it&amp;rsquo;s like a game of rock paper scissors, but instead it&amp;rsquo;s earth, fire, frost and lightning. Where Earth defeats lightning, fire defeats earth and frost defeats fire. I&amp;rsquo;ll go into all mechanics in depth and then come back to elaborate on this analogy.
Earthen pillar | Opalfang Earthen Pillar spawn on targeted players doing some damage.</description></item><item><title>Eranog</title><link>https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/eranog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:07:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://realret.github.io/voi/posts/eranog/</guid><description>Allright the first boss we will be taking on is Eranog. The fight has 2 phases with only a small amount of mechanics. First off is a mechanic thats present in all phases: adds that spawn we will kill those by kiting them to the boss.
Phase 1 During phase 1 the raid stands behind the boss and wacks it a bunch. While wacking the boss there are three mechanics to deal with wich are:</description></item></channel></rss>